JEREMY CRUMP

http://jeremycrump.work

SUMMARY

I'm currently enrolled at MATC studying Web and Software Development.

Web development is an exciting and fulfilling experience. After 10 years of working as a chef in the restaurant industry I have acquired swift critical thinking skills and team mentality required to be successful in the ever growing technology field. The surplus of knowledge to gain, problem solving scenarios, and the creative aspects of software and web development are just a few examples of the things I love about this industry.

WEB DEVELOPMENT COURSES

Sept. 2019 Udemy - The Complete Javascript Course 2020 - Jonas Schmedtman

Studied Asynchronous JavaScript, DOM manipulation, and ES6 basic fundamentals.

Also, gained basic knowledge of NPM, Babel, nodeJS, and Webpack.

Jan. 2018 FreeCodeCamp

Studied Basic JavaScript ES5 fundamentals. Studied HTML 5 and CSS. Learned how to make websites responsive for mobile devices using media queries. Built static web

forms. Created a base portfolio using CSS flexbox.

SKILLS

NETBEANS C#
SQL
JAVA

VISUAL STUDIO JAVASCRIPT
VISUAL STUDIO CODE HTML5

EDUCATION

Aug 2020 - Present Milwaukee Area Technical College

CSS

A.A.S - IT WEB/SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT

EMPLOYMENT

Apr. 2018 - Present The Molding Group - Line Engineer - Kenosha

Maintaining an inventory of 200 parts for water filtration company. Shipping and receiving orders daily. Quality control of manufactured parts.

Feb. 2016 - Apr. 2018 Odd Duck Restaurant · Sous Chef · Milwaukee

Team leader for kitchen staff of a busy, high volume restaurant. Creating menu items using sustainable food practices and utilizing products from local farmers. Managing inventory of all food related products in restaurant. Time management. Training staff.